你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
上一个视频，你直接进入并使用Linux操作系统上最强大的工具。
The last video you got stuck right in and use the most powerful tool on the Linux operating system.
但正如他们所说，强大的力量伴随着巨大的责任。
But as they say with great power comes great responsibility.
因此，为了最大限度地控制Linux操作系统，您需要对
So in order to maximize your control over the Linux operating system you need to get a solid understanding
当你输入你的命令时会发生什么。
of what's going on when you type your commands.
在接下来的几个视频中，我们将对实际发生的事情做一些深入的研究
So over the next few videos we're going to be doing a bit of a deep dive on what is actually going on
当您运行命令时，还可以详细了解命令的结构，以便您可以
when you run your commands and also go into detail on how the commands are structured so that you can
了解如何正确使用它们。
understand how to use them properly.
现在，如果你已经有过一些以前的经验，但感觉不是很有经验，或者什么都没有
Now if you do already have some previous experience but didn't feel as you quite got it or that something
在你的理解中是缺失的，很可能你不是百分之百清楚
is missing in your understanding it's very likely that you aren't 100 percent clear on the stuff that
我们将在接下来的几个视频中进行报道。
we're going to be covering in the next few videos.
所以这是非常重要的事情。
So this is super important stuff.
现在，不管你以前有过什么经验，还是完全是个初学者，我真的希望你付钱
Now whether you do have some previous experience or a complete beginner to it I really want you to pay
我们将在接下来的几个视频中介绍的主题将是您最关注的主题，因为它们是如此
your best attention to the topics that we'll be covering in the next few videos because they are so
对您理解Linux操作系统至关重要。
critically important to your understanding of the Linux operating system.
如果您理解我们在接下来的几个视频中介绍的内容，那么您在Linux中所做的一切都将开始
And if you do understand what we cover in the next few videos everything you do in Linux will start
才能说得更有意义。
to make a whole lot more sense.
所以让我们非常非常兴奋的是，我们将会把这些事情弄清楚。
So be very very excited that we're going to clear this stuff up.
现在，在这段视频中，您将了解终端命令和名为
Now in this video you're going to learn the difference between commands the terminal and something called
贝壳。
the shell.
这些都是非常重要的区别，它们将基本上支撑你所做的每一件事
These are very important distinctions that will underpin basically every single thing that you do on
命令行。
the command line.
在本视频结束时，您将了解终端命令和
And by the end of this video you'll have understood the difference between the terminal commands and
外壳，您将对其背后的实际情况有更丰富、更深入的理解
the shell and you'll have a much richer and deeper understanding of what is actually going on behind
场景。
the scenes.
当你使用航站楼的时候。
When you use the terminal.
所以这将是一场极其重要的讲座。
So this is going to be a critically important lecture.
让我们继续往前走，开始做这件事吧。
Let's go ahead and get into it.
那么，当我们键入命令时，实际上发生了什么。
So what is actually going on when we type a command.
要理解这一点，我们需要知道命令和所谓的shell之间的区别。
Well to understand this we need to know the difference between a command and something called the shell.
这些命令只是文本。
The commands are just text.
但是当你按Enter键时，文本的意思就会由一个叫做外壳的计算机程序来解释。
But when you press enter the meaning of that text is interpreted by a computer program called the shell.
好的。
OK.
让我们举一个真实世界的例子。
So let's take a real world example.
如果我们在左边的rasboras上看到这个词，在物理层面上，这个词就是字母是a
If we see the word here on the left rasboras on a physical level that word is just the letters are a
s p b e r e s，就像任何其他单词一样。
s p b e r r r e s and just like any other word.
如果你不懂这门语言，它对你就没有多大意义。
If you can't read the language it won't mean much to you.
对，但是如果你用了这个词，比如说你可以读英语，那么你会发生什么呢？
Right but if you took this word and you could for example read English then what would happen is you
你会看到那篇文章，你会解读它的意思吗，可能会出来的是这个
would you would see that text and you would interpret it for meaning and what might come out is this
水果。
fruit.
好的，你会看到这段文字，你会把它和这个水果，树莓相匹配。
Ok you'd see that text and you would match it with this fruit the raspberries.
但是，在将文本解释成具体含义的过程中，有一个过程，那就是
But there's a process in the middle of interpreting that text into specific meaning and that is the
贝壳的工作。
job of the shell.
好的。
OK.
为了更清楚一点，我们假设你接受了“礼物”这个词。
So to make this a bit clearer let's say you took the word gift.
好的。
OK.
你用英语阅读这个单词，可能会产生这样的意思
And you read that word using the English language and the meaning that might come out might be the idea
在某人生日时送他们礼物或其他东西。
of giving someone a present or something on their birthday.
好的，所以你可能会说，你可能会从阅读“礼物”这个词中得到这个意思，而不是
Ok so you might say you might get this meaning coming out from reading the word gift but instead of
用英语用英语读它，用英语外壳。
reading it in English with an English shell.
所以我们叫它，假设你拿了完全相同的单词礼物，但是这一次你和一个德国人一起读到了它
So we call it let's say you took exactly the same word gift but this time you read it with a German
壳。
shell.
现在，如果你用德语阅读礼物，而不是一份礼物，它可能会表达出这样的意思
Now instead of a present coming out the meaning that might come out of that if you read it in German
可能是毒药，讽刺的是，这不是最好的礼物，但你可以在这里看到，文本完全是
would be the poison which is ironically not the best gift but you can see here that the text is exactly
同样的，但根据解释它的外壳的不同，表达出来的意思是不同的。
the same but the meaning that comes out is different depending upon the shell that interpreted it.
好的。
OK.
再举一个例子，假设我们把单词Smoking(吸烟)放在英语外壳里再读一遍
As another example let's say we took the word smoking smoking if you read that again in an English shell
它的意思将会是使用香烟的想法。
the meaning that would come out would be the idea of using a cigarette.
但是如果你取了完全相同的单词，在这段时间里，它通过了一个法语外壳。
But if you took exactly the same word and in this time passed it through a French shell.
好的。
OK.
在这里使用人类解释的类比，出来的将是一件燕尾服，这是一种奇特的东西。
Using the analogy here of human interpretation what would come out would be a tuxedo which is a fancy
衣服的类型。
type of clothing.
所以您可以在这里看到文本可以完全相同，但是shell解释文本可以提供给它
So you can see here the text can be exactly the same but the shell interprets that text can give it
不同的意思，这在你的电脑上是完全相同的。
different meaning and that is exactly the same on your computer.
那么，我们现在了解的命令和shell之间的区别的终端又如何呢？
So what about the terminal that we now understand the difference between a command and the shell.
那么航站楼是用来做什么的。
So what's the terminal for.
航站楼不过是打开外壳的一扇窗而已。
Well the terminal is nothing more than just a window into the shell.
所以让我们把这个变得更容易理解一些。
So let's make this a bit easier to understand.
所以，如果我问你，你会如何在不打开终端的情况下在节目中键入命令呢？
So if I asked you how would you type commands on to your show without opening the terminal Well you
写不出来。
couldn't write.
这就是终端这个术语，有点像中间的部分，使用
And that's exactly what the terminal is the term that is kind of like the middle piece in between using
在键入命令的间隙出来，并将它们召唤到shell。
come out in between typing commands and summon them to the shell.
您不能在任何地方真正键入命令，除非您打开了一个终端，这就是您要做的
You can't really type commands anywhere unless you've opened a terminal and that's all is what you're
所做的是在终端中键入命令，然后按Enter键，然后将它们提交到
doing is you're typing commands in the terminal and you press enter and then they are submitted to the
航站楼的架子有点像中间的部分。
shelves of the terminal is kind of like the middle piece.
好的。
OK.
实际上有不同类型的贝壳，所以不同类型的货架就像
And there are actually different types of shells so different types of shelves just like there were
不同类型的人类语言实际上可以用不同的方式解释相同的命令。
different types of human languages can actually interpret the same command in different ways.
但幸运的是，有一种外壳类型已经出现，这是最常见的类型，称为
But fortunately there is one type of shell which has been which is the most common type which is called
重击炮弹。
the bash shell.
因此，如果您曾经听说过术语bash shell脚本或bash脚本或类似的东西，它的意思是
So if you've ever heard the term bash shell scripting or bash scripting or something like that it means
编写bash shell和Linux可以读取的程序和脚本。
writing programs and writing scripts that can be read by the bash shell and Linux.
大多数Linux发行版都使用bash shell，而boon Buntu在默认情况下肯定是这样做的。
Most Linux distribution use the bash shell and aboon buntu definitely does by default.
所以这一点需要记住，Linux上有不同类型的shell。
So that's something to bear in mind that there are different types of shells on Linux.
它们可以用不同的方式解释命令，但最常见的是bash shell。
They can interpret commands in different ways but the most common one is the bash shell.
所以我们就是这样，我们在那里有一些标准化。
So there we are we've got some standardization there.
总而言之，命令a RealAge就是您在终端中键入的文本，当您按Enter键时
So to summarize commands a RealAge the text that you type in the terminal and when you press enter that
文本由外壳解释。
text is interpreted by the shell.
现在外壳是一个将文本转换成计算机操作的程序。
Now the shell is a program that translates that text into into actions for the computer.
现在，这意味着不同的shell实际上可以不同地解释相同的文本，这可能会导致
Now this means that different shells can actually interpret the same text differently which might cause
有些问题，但幸运的是，大多数Linux机器都使用bash shell。
some problems but fortunately most Linux machines use the bash shell.
因此，大多数机器都是一致的，正如我们所说的，终端只是一个窗口
So there is consistency across most machines and as we said as well the terminal is just a window to
shell只是中间的一部分，它允许您键入命令并将它们提交到
the shell it just it's just the middle piece that allows you to type your commands and submit them to
贝壳。
the shell.
作为额外的一条信息，您的命令实际上也区分大小写。
And as a bonus piece of information your commands are actually also case sensitive.
因此，如果您键入全大写的命令(如果shell不期望看到该命令)，则很可能
So if you type a command in all uppercase if the shell isn't expecting to see that it will probably
给你一个错误。
give you an error.
因此，您需要确保拼写方式完全正确。
So you need to make sure that things are spelled in exactly the correct way.
好的，它的好处是允许您有更多的选择，因为细微的差异可以
OK which has the benefits of allowing you to have more more options because slight differences can give
不同的功能，但这意味着在实际键入命令时必须非常小心
different functionality but it means you have to be really careful on how you actually type your commands
如果你想让他们按照你想要的方式工作。
if you want them to work the way you want them to.
接下来，因为我们将在本课程中花费大量时间键入命令
Now what's coming up next is because we're going to spend a lot of the time in this course typing commands
并将它们提交给外壳。
and submitting them to the shell.
我不想让你们学完这门课，只需要记住装货、装货和装货的不同
I don't want you to go through this course and just have to memorize loads and loads and loads different
就像几乎所有其他原因一样，命令会让你做你要做的事情，那就是我们要
commands just like pretty much every other cause makes you do what you're going to do is we're going
花点时间了解命令的实际内容以及它们的结构，以便您
to take a bit of time to understand what commands actually are and how they are structured so that you
我可以开始看到每件事背后的模式，你可以开始将命令视为一种语言类型
can start to see a pattern behind everything you can start to look at the commands as a type of language
而不是你必须记住的屏幕上的随机文本。
rather than just random text on the screen that you've got to memorize.
现在很可能你们以前没有看过这个，所以这将是一个完整的游戏
Now it's likely you'll probably not have been shown this before so this is going to be a complete game
改变您学习Linux操作系统和学习终端的实际方式。
changer in how you actually approach learning the Linux operating system and learning the terminal.
所以我真的迫不及待地想向你们展示这个，这将是非常有帮助的。
So I really can't wait to show you this it's going to be really really really helpful.
好了，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
So for all that goodness I'll see you in the next video.